sheerluxe.com 2008-06-17

# Privacy policy - SheerLuxe.com

|   
At SheerLuxe.com ("SheerLuxe"), we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices and policy regarding the collection and use of information (including personally identifiable information) made available to us through the www.sheerluxe.com website (the "SheerLuxe Site"). 

You are, of course, free to use the majority of the SheerLuxe Site without providing any information to us. However, to the extent that you or other users do provide or make available any information to us, that information can generally be categorized as either anonymous or personally identifiable. Anonymous information is information that cannot be traced back to a specific individual. Personally identifiable information is information from which you or another individual can be identified. This information can include your name, email, address, postcode, age, etc. 

**Opt In**  
When you register as a member of SheerLuxe.com or sign up for any of the services that we offer to members or other users on a subscription basis, for example, newsletters and/or email communications about news and events ("Services") you will be asked to 'opt in' to our Privacy Policy i.e. to confirm that you agree to our use of any personally identifiable information that we may collect from you or be provided with by you in connection with your use of the SheerLuxe.com Site. By 'opting-in' you agree to our use of your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not provide your consent, you will not be able to become a member of SheerLuxe.com and/or use the Services. If you do subscribe to any of our Services you may also unsubscribe from the relevant distribution list(s) at any time. You may also withdraw your consent to our use of any other personally identifiable information that we hold on you at any time. If you wish to unsubscribe from our Services or withdraw any consent that you have previously provided to our use of your personally identifiable information, please see paragraph 12 below (Unsubscribing, Correction and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information).   
Our privacy policy is simple.

### 1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable

**Information**  
SheerLuxe collects the details provided by you when you register as a member of SheerLuxe.com or sign up for any of our Services together with any personally identifiable information we learn about you through your use of the Services. For example, we may collect additional personally identifiable information through your participation in any promotions and competitions offered by us.   
We will notify our members when we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy that affect the use of any personally identifiable information we collect. We will not make new use of any personally identifiable information which SheerLuxe gathered from individual members or users prior to any such change in our Privacy Policy without first obtaining the member's or user's consent for any new uses. 

### 2\. Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is a priority to us. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the internet, can be guaranteed to be 100 per cent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and our servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the SheerLuxe Site. You provide all such information at your own risk.

### 3\. Newsletter and Email Communications Subscribers

If you decide not to become a member of SheerLuxe.com but wish to subscribe to one or more of our newsletters or email communications services, we will need to collect your email address in order to send our newsletters and/or email communications to you. We will not use your email address for any purpose except in connection with sending you the newsletters and/or emails you have requested, maintaining our subscription and unsubscription lists, communicating with you in the event of a change in the ownership of SheerLuxe or its business, or notifying you of changes to the SheerLuxe Site, business practices, Terms of Service or Privacy Policy, unless (i) we are required to do so by applicable law or pursuant to a court or similar order; (ii) as deemed necessary, in SheerLuxe discretion, to protect the legal rights or the property of SheerLuxe, a member or third party, or to prevent personal injury; or (iii) you have provided your consent for us to do so.

### 4\. Sensitive Personally Identifiable Information

It is possible that the selections you make or information that you provide when using our Services may indicate information about you that is sensitive such as the state of your health or your sexual orientation. As with all of the personally identifiable information you provide to us, you can be assured that any sensitive information you choose to supply to us will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and/or applicable law.

### 5\. How we use the Personally Identifiable  
Information you provide

We use the personally identifiable information we collect to supply our Services to you. We may also use your contact details to communicate with you (including without limitation in the event of a change in ownership of SheerLuxe or its business, our business practices, or our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy). Except where you have asked us not to, we may contact you by email, post, text message or telephone. We may also use your personally identifiable information to send you information, special offers, promotions, coupons and free samples whether on behalf of ourselves or our group companies or on behalf of carefully selected third parties.

### 6\. Disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information

We may disclose your personally identifiable information in the following instances: (i) if we are required to do so by applicable law or pursuant to a court or similar order; (ii) as deemed necessary, in SheerLuxe discretion, to protect the legal rights or the property of SheerLuxe, a member or third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or (iii) in connection with a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or stock of SheerLuxe or its affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). In addition, SheerLuxe reserves the right to allow access to its systems to third parties providing necessary technical services when such access is required in order to provide those services and to provide your personally identifiable information to third parties who provide services on behalf of SheerLuxe, provided that such third parties are bound by SheerLuxe Privacy Policy. 

### 7\. Other Web Sites

Where we provide links to third party web sites (whether or not they are affiliated with SheerLuxe and even if SheerLuxe branding appears on these sites), such sites are not controlled by us and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These links are provided for your convenience only. If you access these sites by using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy. Although where possible we endeavour to ensure that the site operators abide by our Privacy Policy, we cannot guarantee that they will and you are advised to check the privacy policy of such third parties before providing information to them. 

### 8\. Cookie

Use of Cookies on our Site   
A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are.   
A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the 'lifetime' of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.   
Two types of cookies are used on this website:   
session cookies - temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site;   
persistent cookies - these remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).   
Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies.

How we use cookies on our website and what information we collect  
Session cookies: 

  * To allow you to carry information across pages of our site and avoid having to log-in many times.   

  * Within registration to allow you to access stored information.   
Persistent cookies:   

  * To help us recognise you as a unique visitor (just a number) when you return to our website and to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to avoid showing you the same adverts repeatedly.   

  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.   

  * Within research surveys to ensure you are not invited to complete a questionnaire too often or after you have already done so.   

  * To store registration information so that if you are a member you only have to re-enter your password (instead of all your registration information) each time you visit the site, and so that the site can recognise you as a member.   

We do not pass any personally identifiable information obtained by cookie use to third party advertising companies.   
Third-party cookies:   
Third parties serve cookies via this site. These are used for the following purposes:  

  * To serve advertisements on our site and track whether these advertisements are clicked on by users.   

  * To control how often you are shown a particular advertisement.   

  * To tailor content to your preferences.   

  * To count the number of anonymous users of our site.   

  * To aggregate anonymised information for marketing purposes.  

Use of web beacons   
Some of our web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information which including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third-party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign. 

**Disabling or enabling cookies**  
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled. 

### 9\. Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Other Public Forums

Please note that our forums are open to the public and if you choose to disclose personally identifiable information in these areas you are consenting to its unrestricted distribution in a public forum throughout SheerLuxe.com and to and by other SheerLuxe.com members. We therefore cannot be responsible for the protection or security of such information, regardless of its sensitivity. You disclose all such information on our bulletin boards or in our chat rooms or other public forums entirely at your own risk. 

### 10\. Third Party Personally Identifiable Information

You must not disclose personally identifiable information relating to any third party on our bulletin boards or in our chat rooms or other public forums or in conjunction with any Service (for example, when using our postcard service) unless you have their express consent to do so.

### 11\. General

Your personally identifiable information will be held and used by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy and UK data protection legislation. You have a right to access the personally identifiable information that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personally identifiable information SheerLuxe holds about you please contact us via email with your name and address.   
By using the SheerLuxe Site, you confirm your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, incorporated herein by this reference. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the SheerLuxe Site and do not register for any of the Services. Subject to the provisions above regarding material changes to this Privacy Policy, which we will notify you of, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice (including, without limitation, on the introduction of new services to our users which affect our privacy practices). Any such change will take effect once the revised privacy policy is available on SheerLuxe.com. You will be bound by any such changes to the Privacy Policy. Therefore, we ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure your continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the SheerLuxe Site following such changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes. You can determine when this policy was last revised by checking the "Last Revised" legend at the top of this Privacy Policy.

### 12\. Unsubscribing, Correction and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information on our database amended or deleted, please contact us at [customerservice@sheerluxe.com](mailto:customerservice@sheerluxe.com), and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with your request in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. (We may need to contact you or verify who you are in order to be sure that we are deleting or changing the appropriate information).   
To unsubscribe from Newsletters [click here ](http://www.sheerluxe.com/myprofile.htm "click here")  
To unsubscribe altogether from our database, please contact [customerservice@sheerluxe.com](mailto:customerservice@sheerluxe.com)  
When requesting that personally identifiable information be amended or deleted, please keep in mind that there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes. However, we may use that information, from time to time, to recontact former members or visitors to the SheerLuxe Site in certain limited circumstances - for instance, if required to do so by law. 

### 13\. Queries

If you have any queries about this privacy policy, please email us at [customerservice@sheerluxe.com](mailto:customerservice@sheerluxe.com) | 

Enter your email address below to sign up for FREE
